const questions = [
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following sets of web technologies is Thong most likely to be proficient in, given his background in full-stack development?",
    choices: [
      "HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node.js, and SQL",
      "Ruby, Rails, PHP, and MongoDB",
      "Python, Django, Flask, and GraphQL",
      "Swift, Kotlin, React Native, and Firebase",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following best describes Thong Nguyen's educational background?",
    choices: [
      "Bachelor's in Physics with a minor in Computer Science",
      "Bachelor's in Mathematics with a minor in Physics",
      "Bachelor's in Computer Science with a minor in Mathematics",
      "Bachelor's in Actuarial Sciences with a minor in Computer Science",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What honor did Thong Nguyen receive upon graduating from the University of North Texas?",
    choices: [
      "Magna Cum Laude",
      "Summa Cum Laude",
      "Cum Laude",
      "Valedictorian",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which programming languages does Thong Nguyen have expertise?",
    choices: [
      "Python, Ruby, and Go",
      "C++, C, Java, Python and JavaScript",
      "C#, Swift, and Kotlin",
      "PHP, Perl, and R",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What was Thong Nguyen's ranking in the Mathematics Competition for Community College students in the Southwest Region in 2019?",
    choices: ["1st place", "2nd place", "3rd place", "4th place"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following areas has Thong Nguyen NOT worked on projects in during his school years?",
    choices: [
      "Web development",
      "Game development",
      "Machine learning",
      "Blockchain technology",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "How many problems has Thong Nguyen solved on LeetCode?",
    choices: ["Over 700", "Over 900", "Over 1100", "Over 1400"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Before settling on Software Engineering, which field did Thong Nguyen NOT explore?",
    choices: [
      "Physics",
      "Mathematics",
      "Actuarial Sciences",
      "Chemical Engineering",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What on-campus job did Thong Nguyen hold during his college years?",
    choices: [
      "Teaching Assistant",
      "Research Assistant",
      "Library Assistant",
      "Science Tutor",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "In which year did Thong Nguyen graduate from a Physics Gifted Class with the highest GPA in his province?",
    choices: ["2014", "2015", "2016", "2017"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following best describes Thong Nguyen's approach to technology and challenges?",
    choices: [
      "Prefers to stick with familiar technologies",
      "Eager to learn new technologies and ready for challenges",
      "Focuses solely on web development technologies",
      "Avoids challenging projects",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
];

export default questions;
